# **MATEUSZ KLUCZEK**

#### **Personal details**

I am self-motivated, committed and determined in achieving my goals. I have clear, logical mind with a practical approach to problem solving. I have firm sense of responsibility developed as an independent researcher abroad. Now I am very interested in machine learning, AI and developing my carrier in that direction.

Nationality: Polish

Email: <u>kluczek.m@gmail.com</u> www: mateusz-kluczek.github.io

phone: +48786635730

## **Research Experience**

I gained my experience as an independent researcher at international institutes. I started research as a student in Poland. I conducted standalone research in applied mathematics and graduated with a PhD degree in Ireland. Afterwards, I worked as an independent researcher in Israel. The research was fully funded by international research institutions. The research was heavily dependent on numerical simulations.

November 2019 – November 2021 <u>The Technion, Haifa, Israel</u>

- Development of standalone research of complex systems of equations
- Development of solving algorithms and scripts in C++
- Analysis of outcome data using C/C++ extensions
- Increasing the impact of the research by developing it in a new, unexplored direction

October 2015 – September 2019

University College Cork, Cork, Ireland

- Independent research in interdisciplinary Applied Mathematics
- Exact solutions of system of nonlinear equations
- Visual representation of the solutions using MATLAB or Mathematica
- Experience in conducting research in big collaborative groups

August 2014 – September 2015 Siedlce University of Natural Sciences and Humanities, Poland

- Interdisciplinary research in Applied Mathematics
- Developing algorithms in MATALB solving particle transport equation
- Implementation of new methods of solutions to already existing algorithms
- Analysis of the resulting data and its visual representation (physical aspects and as well data graphs)

## **Training courses**

- SQL Essential Training (LinkedIn.com)
- Combining and shaping data (Pluralsight.com)
- Representing, Processing, and Preparing Data (Pluralsight.com)
- Summarizing Data and Deducing Probabilities (Pluralsight.com)
- Prolog (in progress)
- Google Cloud Big Data and Machine Learning Fundamentals

#### Education

October 2015 – September 2019 Funded PhD in Applied Mathematics

University College Cork, Cork, Ireland

October 2010 – September 2015 Bachelor and master's degree in Applied Mathematics

Siedlce University of Natural Sciences and Humanities,

Poland

## **Supplementary experience**

 Teaching experience in delivering tutorials as well as lectures to students at university level

• Teaching experience at the secondary stage of education

• Stock market trader – professional training

• Business sector experience:

March 2015 - September 2015 <u>ING BANK SLASKI, Warsaw, Poland as Auditor</u>

June 2012 - August 2012 BANK BGZ PNB PARIBAS, Siedlce, Poland student placement

# **Knowledge/Skills/Hobbies**

• Programming: MATLAB, Mathematica, LATEX, PASCAL, C++/C, JAVA & SQL (in progress).

• Win: 7, 8, 10, 11. MACOS, IOS. MS Office: 2010, 2013, 365.

• Languages: Polish (nativ), English (fluent), German (basic).

• Responsibility, loyalty, independence. Ability to cope with difficult situations. Good manners.

• Dedicated and flexible.

Knowledge of blockchain and cryptocurrency concept.

- Adobe Lightroom, Photoshop creating of photobooks and photo editing.
- Music, movies, psychology and human behaviour podcasts, strength training, healthy and eco-orientated lifestyle.
- Studying Hebrew and interested in the middle east culture